DEMI HAYASHI

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE ENGINEER

Q Los Angeles, CA

hayashi.demi@gmail.com

561-713-5699

github.com/demivlkv



demihayashi.com

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A motivated Full-Stack Developer with proficiency in the MERN (MongoDB, Express.js, React.js, and Node.js) tech stack and passion for UX/UI. Dedicated to writing efficient, high-performance code that prioritizes user experience and accessibility. Self-sufficient quick learner and inspired team-player with extensive experience in prioritizing the clients' needs and working effectively in both team and independent settings.

WORK EXPERIENCE

SOFTWARE ENGINEER @ NEXALURE TECHNOLOGIES (Jan 2024 - Present)

- » Lead the development of front-end and full-stack solutions using TypeScript, React, Redux, NextJS, Node, MongoDB, and SCSS, creating dynamic, responsive user interfaces optimized for contemporary web browsers
- » Collaborate in a 9-member in Agile team, contributing to stand-ups, sprint planning, estimation, and retrospectives, fostering a culture of excellence through proactive engagement and effective teamwork
- » Manage Git for version control, resolving complex merge conflicts to ensure smooth and efficient team collaboration in a fast-paced development environment
- » Actively contribute in code reviews and conduct pair programming, cultivating a collaboration, providing constructive feedback, and improving code quality and maintainability

FREELANCE WEB DEVELOPER @ TOKIO RAMEN (Mar 2020 - Dec 2023)

- » Engineered and revamped a dynamic front-end web application for a local ramen shop using JavaScript, Gatsby.js, GraphQL, Tailwind CSS, and Contentful, increasing website traffic by 40% and enhancing user engagement by 50%
- » Revamped company's visual identity with a new logo, menus, and digital content, resulting in a 20% increase in brand recognition
- » Improved website functionality by 25% through key solutions, enhancing user experience and increasing customer satisfaction

PROJECTS

TRIP TIDE (December 2022 - March 2023)

» Developed a travel-themed MERN-stack web application serving as a comprehensive resource for travel-related information and discussion for travel enthusiasts using React, Tailwind CSS, MongoDB, & GraphQL to handle user interactivity, protection of sensitive user information, and data manipulation

BOOK NOOK (September 2022)

» Participated in a collaboration with 5 developers to construct a MERN-stack web application, where users can discuss books, search books, and get book recommendations from other users; played a key role in designing and implementing the user interface,

SKILLS

LANGUAGES

» JavaScript (ES6+), TypeScript, CSS3, HTML5

TECHNOLOGIES

» React.js, Next.js, Node.js, Express.js, Redux, REST APIs, GraphQL, Sass/SCSS, Contentful Headless CMS, jQuery, Bootstrap, Tailwind CSS, Materialize

DATABASES

» MySQL, MongoDB

TOOLS

» Git, GitHub, Vite.js, Heroku, npm, Figma, Sketch, Adobe Photoshop

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF FLORIDA

- » Bachelor of Fine Arts
- » Concentration in Creative Photography
- » Graduated Cum Laude

UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

- » Full-Stack Coding Bootcamp
- » Certificate of Completion

FOREIGN LANGUAGES

JAPANESE

» Native proficiency